in previous tutorials I demonstrated how
在前面的教程中，我演示了如何
you can wrap text around simple shapes
您可以将文本环绕在简单形状周围
like a circle by using the place on text
通过使用文本上的位置像一个圆圈
command however in this tutorial I'm
命令，但在本教程中，我是
going to show you how you can wrap text
我将向您展示如何对文本进行换行
around more complicated shapes such as a
围绕着更复杂的形状，如
heart and to show you what I mean if I
并向你展示我的意思，如果我
were to select both of these objects
要同时选择这两个对象
here and go to text and select put on
在这里，转到文本并选择穿上
path you can see we don't get a very
你可以看到，我们没有一个非常好的
good outcome we don't get to choose the
很好的结果我们不用选择
placement of the text on the path it
文本在路径上的放置它
just randomly chooses it and you can't
只是随机地选择它，你不能
choose a different start or end point
选择不同的起点或终点
for this text so to get this result what
对于这篇文章来说，要得到这个结果是什么
we're going to do is we're going to
我们要做的是我们要
create separate paths for each half of
为的每一半创建单独的路径
the heart and then create separate lines
心，然后创建单独的线条
of text for each path so let me get
每条路径的文本，所以让我
started on that I'm going to grab my
从那开始我要拿起我的
selection tool and instead of placing
选择工具，而不是放置
the text directly on this path I'm going
我要走的这条路径上的文本
to place it on a copy of the path so I'm
把它放在路径的副本上，这样我就
going to create a linked offset I'm
要创建链接的偏移，我要
actually going to create an offset copy
实际上要创建一个偏移拷贝
of the shape so I could place the text
形状，这样我就可以放置文本
around the outside padding of the shape
在形状的外部填充周围
instead of placing it directly on top of
而不是直接把它放在
the shape so let me select this object I
形状，所以让我选择这个对象
will go to path and I will select linked
将转到路径，我将选择链接
offset and then I will go to my nodes
偏移，然后我将转到我的节点
tool and I will pull this node out to
工具，我将把这个节点拉出到
create a little bit of an offset and I
创建一点偏移量，然后我
will give this a different color just so
会给这件衣服带来不同的颜色
I could differentiate it from the
我可以把它和
original shape and I'll pull this out to
原来的形状，我会把它拉出来
about
关于
there and now I'm going to convert this
现在我要把这个转换成
to a path by going to path object to
通过转到路径对象到路径
path and I want to apply a stroke to
Path和我想要将笔划应用到
this so let me grab my selection tool
这让我拿起我的选择工具
I'm going to hold the shift key and I'm
我要按住Shift键，然后我
going to click the letter or the color
要点击字母或颜色
blue just to apply a blue stroke and
蓝色只是为了应用蓝色的笔触和
then I'm going to remove remove the fill
然后我要移除填充物
color now let me make that stroke a
颜色现在让我把这一笔画成
little smaller I'm going to open up my
再小一点，我要打开我的
fill and stroke menu by double clicking
通过双击填充和描边菜单
this stripe down here I'll go to the
这条条纹在这里，我要去
stroke style Tab and I'm just going to
笔划样式选项卡和我要做的
make that
就这么定了
one so the approach I'm going to use
一，所以我将使用的方法
here is I'm going to break this up into
这就是我要把它分解成
separate pads and then Place separate
分开焊盘，然后分开放置
lines on each path so let me select this
每条路径上的线条，让我选择这个
object and I'm going to go to my nodes
对象，我将转到我的节点
tool and I want to select this node
工具和我想要选择此节点
right here and I want to break the path
就在这里，我想打破这条道路
at that node so I'll come up here to
在那个节点上，所以我会到这里来
this icon that says break path at
此图标显示在以下位置中断路径
selected nodes when you your cursor over
将光标悬停在选定节点上时
and I'll click on that and nothing Vis
我会点击它，没有任何
visibly changes on your screen but the
在屏幕上发生了明显的变化，但
path has now been broken up into
路径现在已被分解为
separate nodes as you can see there and
如您在那里看到的，分隔节点
I'll come down here and do the same
我会下来做同样的事
thing I Want to Break these paths up as
我想把这些路径分解为
well so let me select those and I'm
好的，那么让我选择这些，然后我
going to break those paths as well and
也会打破这些障碍
now I'm going to break apart the entire
现在我要把整个
shape so let me go back to my select
所以让我回到我的选择
tool I will go to path and select break
工具I将转到路径并选择中断
apart and now I can just take this
分开了，现在我可以带着这个
little piece down here and get rid of
在这里放一小块，然后扔掉
this and if you can see now we have
如果你能看到我们现在有
separate paths for each half of the
的每一半都有不同的路径
shape and what I'm going to do is create
形状，我要做的是创造
separate lines of text one line of text
将文本行分隔开一行文本
going on this side and another line
走在这一边和另一条线上
going on this side so I have one line of
在这一边，所以我有一行
text right now I want to break this up
我现在就发短信，我想把这件事分开
into two so let me duplicate this by
一分为二，所以让我重复一下
pressing contrl D or command D if you're
按Ctrl D或Command D
on Mac and the way that I set this up is
在Mac上，我设置的方式是
I had up until the word four going over
我一直到第四个字过去
here and then after that the right side
在这里和那之后，右边
begins so I'm going to end the line of
开始，所以我要结束这行
text after the word four I'm going to
文字后面的四个字我要去
grab my text
抓起我的短信
tool so now that I have my two SE
工具，现在我有了两个SE
separate lines of text I'm going to take
我将使用不同的文本行
this line of text hold shift click on
此行文本按住Shift键并单击
this left path and then go to text and
这条左侧路径，然后转到文本和
select put on
选择穿上
path now we end up with this effect here
路径，现在我们在这里结束这个效果
which is not what I'm going for so I'm
这不是我想要的，所以我
going to click off of that to deselect
要单击该选项以取消选择
it I'm going to select just the path and
如果我只选择这条路
now to place the text on the outside of
现在要将文本放在
the path rather than the inside I'm
我走的是路而不是我的内心
going to reverse the direction of the
将会反转
path so I will go to path and select if
路径，因此我将转到路径并选择
I can find it reverse there it is and
我可以找到它的反转，它在那里
now it's going to put it on the outside
现在它要把它放在外面
so the problem I have now is I have to
所以我现在的问题是我必须
make this text a little bigger to fill
将此文本稍大一些以进行填充
in the rest of this empty space here so
在这片空地的其余地方
let me grab my text tool and I'm going
让我拿起我的文本工具，我要去
to Triple click this text to select it
要进行三次选择，请单击此文本将其选中
and I'm going to make the size of this a
我要把这件事的大小
little bigger I'm going to try something
再大一点，我要试一试
like 30 you see how that looks I'll
大概30岁，你看那是什么样子，我会
increase that maybe
可能会增加这一数字
34 okay 34 looks good whatever size you
34号好的34号看起来不错，不管你穿什么尺寸
use make a mental note what size that is
在脑海中记下它的大小
because we're going to use that same
因为我们要用同样的方法
size for this text object here so that
此处此文本对象的大小，以便
these two lines of text look
这两行文本看起来
consistent so now that's done and I'll
始终如一，现在已经完成了，我将
come over here and do the same thing
到这里来，做同样的事情
I'll select this text object hold shift
我将选择此文本对象按住Shift键
click on the path and go to text and
单击路径并转到文本和
select put on
选择穿上
path now I'm going to have to do the
路径，现在我要做的是
same thing here with the reversing of
这里的情况也是如此，逆转了
the pads I'm going to select the path
我要选择路径的垫子
just the path and go to path and select
只需选择路径，然后转到路径并选择
reverse and then I'll do the same thing
倒车，然后我会做同样的事情
over here I'm going to grab my text tool
在这里，我要拿起我的文本工具
select all the text and I want to make
选择所有文本，我要创建
this the same size I'll make this
这个尺码一样，我要做这个。
34 and I'm going to change the spacing
34并且我要改变间距
of this a little bit I mentioned earlier
我之前提到的这一点
that you can't really change the
你不能真的改变
position of the text on the path you can
文本在路径上的位置
a little bit by adding spacing between
通过在之间添加间距来增加一点
the letters so I'm going to place the
这些字母，所以我要把
cursor before the text and just press my
光标放在文本之前，然后按我的
space bar to add some space in there and
空格键在其中添加一些空格
if you want to add some more space
如果您想要添加更多空间
between individual letters just move
在各个字母之间只是移动
your cursor around with the arrows if
您的光标在以下情况下使用箭头移动
you place the cursor between two letters
你把光标放在两个字母之间
you can hold the ALT key and use your
您可以按住Alt键并使用您的
left and right arrows to increase and
向左和向右箭头以增加和
decrease the spacing between the text or
减小文本之间的间距或
if you're using Mac like me you can use
如果您像我一样使用Mac，您可以使用
the option case so I'm holding option
期权案例，所以我持有期权
and then using my right arrow key to
然后使用我的向右箭头键
increase spacing between the letters and
增加字母和字母之间的间距
the left Arrow key to decrease it
向左箭头键可以减小它
and once you're finished you can grab
一旦你完成了，你就可以抓起
your selection tool if you don't want
您的选择工具，如果您不想
this ugly path sitting in your way you
这条丑陋的小路阻挡着你
can select the path and then turn off
可以选择路径，然后关闭
well make sure you have it selected
好的，一定要把它选好
because it's going to select the text
因为它将选择文本
first I'm going to hold the ALT key or
首先，我要按住Alt键或
the option key and click again so that
Option键并再次单击，以便
it grabs the path rather than the text
它抓住的是路径而不是文本
itself and you'll know you have the path
它本身，你就会知道你有路
selected when you see the colored stripe
当您看到彩色条纹时选择
down there and I'm going to turn off the
在那下面，我要关掉
visibility of that path by holding shift
按住Shift键可查看该路径
and clicking the X and now it's gone and
然后点击X，现在它消失了
I'll do the same thing over here to this
我会在这里对这个做同样的事情
path I will select it
PATH I将选择它
hold shift click the X to turn off the
按住Shift键单击X可关闭
visibility and now the path is no longer
可见性和现在的路径不再是
visible it's still there it's just not
看得见，它仍然在那里，只是不在
visible if you want to see it at any
如果您想在任何时候看到它，都可以看到
point you can just come up here to where
你可以直接从这里走到什么地方
it says view go to display mode and
它说查看转到显示模式并
choose outline overview and you can see
选择大纲概述，您可以看到
where that path is just make sure to go
那条路一定要走到哪里
back to the normal View mode once you're
返回到正常查看模式后，您将
done so let me go to view display mode
完成此操作后，我将进入查看显示模式
and choose normal and there we go if you
如果你选择正常，我们就开始了
found this lesson useful then consider
觉得这一课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的Inkscape大师课
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where I go over all of the the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape and I explain what
Inkscape中的功能，我将向您解释
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示了它们的工作方式
kind of like how I did in this video we
有点像我在这段视频中所做的
even have a private Community where you
甚至拥有一个私人社区，在那里你可以
can ask questions and get help from me
可以问我问题并得到我的帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何你想要的时间，最好的是有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
只需支付每月会员费
$17 one time and you're in for Life I'll
一次17美元，你就终身难忘了，我会
have some information about that down
有一些相关信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想检查一下，请在下面作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看
oh
哦